niharsworld.com 2011-05-11

# Privacy Policy « Nihar's World

### Privacy Policy for www.niharsworld.com

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy while [online](http://www.niharsworld.com/2011/02/16/watch-icc-cricket-world-cup-2011-live-online-free-icc-cricket-world-cup-2011-live-cricket-streaming-links/ "online") at our [site](http://www.niharsworld.com/2008/01/30/whos-on-your-site-find-on-world-map-in-real-time/ "site") [www.niharsworld.com](http://www.niharsworld.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this [Web](http://www.niharsworld.com/category/Web/ "Web") site.

### The Information We Collect

We use statcounter, [google](http://www.niharsworld.com/category/google/ "google") analytics and other hosting service tools to collect the information. This includes [internet](http://www.differencebetween.co.in/technology/difference-between-internet-and-intranet/ "internet") protocol (IP) addresses, [browser](http://www.niharsworld.com/2007/12/07/hide-browser-at-workplace/ "browser") type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. The name and website [URl](http://www.niharsworld.com/2008/01/28/url-alias-for-mozilla-firefox-very-useful-feature/ "URl") are displayed on comments, but email address is secure with us. We do not share it with outside parties

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of [data](http://www.differencebetween.co.in/terms/difference-between-data-and-information/ "data") stored on the user’s computer [tied](http://www.niharsworld.com/2008/04/21/second-tied-test-match-in-the-history-of-cricket-india-v-australia/ "tied") to information about the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to [subscribe](http://www.niharsworld.com/subscribe/ "subscribe") to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Copy Limitations

Please don’t copy the whole post. A short paragraph with content in quotes is acceptable with a link-back to the post at NiharsWorld.com

### Credit the Source

You need to clearly highlight the fact that the content was derived from NiharsWorld.com

### Link Back

You need to link back to the article from which you derived the excerpt.

### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Axill, Adbrite etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [Contact us](http://www.niharsworld.com/contact-me/ "Contact Us").
